Guide to the Radio TV Services Records, circa 1937-2012 UA.27.02.0001
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Film and Video, circa 1937-1987 and undated
  - Film, 1936-1979
    - Freshman Reception, circa 1960; 16mm, color, silent; 0:02:22
      - Original 16mm motion picture film (Oversize-film-can 6, Film-reel UA27020001-F16-0228)
      - Digital video preservation file (Digital-materials UA27020001-SET-0133, Video-file UA27020001-F16-0228.mkv)
      - Digital video access file (Digital-materials UA27020001-SET-0133, Video-file UA27020001-F16-0228.mp4)
    - Home Security Commercials, circa 1960; 16mm, black-and-white, sound; 0:03:11
      - Original 16mm motion picture film (Oversize-film-can 6, Film-reel UA27020001-F16-0231)
      - Digital video preservation file (Digital-materials UA27020001-SET-0136, Video-file UA27020001-F16-0231.mkv)
      - Digital video access file (Digital-materials UA27020001-SET-0136, Video-file UA27020001-F16-0231.mp4)
    - Home Security Commercials, circa 1960; 16mm, black-and-white, sound; 0:02:10
      - Original 16mm motion picture film (Oversize-film-can 6, Film-reel UA27020001-F16-0232)
      - Digital video preservation file (Digital-materials UA27020001-SET-0137, Video-file UA27020001-F16-0232.mkv)
      - Digital video access file (Digital-materials UA27020001-SET-0137, Video-file UA27020001-F16-0232.mp4)
    - unlabeled, 1960s
      1 film, no reel, no core, in 7 inch can.; Numbered: C-7
      - Original 16mm motion picture film (Box 13, Film-reel UA27020001-F16-0017)
    - Football: Duke - Navy Sports Film with Sound, 1960s
      1 film on core in 10-inch can.; Numbered: C-130
      - Original 16mm motion picture film (Box 37, Film-reel UA27020001-F16-0038)
    - U.S.S. Monitor Discovery, 1960s
      1 film reel: col.; 3 inch, in 7 inch can.; Note on reel: Alcoa Seaprobe on Sat. in later March, 1974, when it was to [sic] public inspection. Note on can: Color Original. See file cards for detailed contents of each reel. Each reel is labeled in abbreviated fashion.; Numbered: C-164-A, Reel 1 of 3; Duplication Master: Beta SP. UA88-57-4
      - Original 16mm motion picture film (Box 15, Film-reel UA27020001-F16-0057)
    - U.S.S. Monitor Discovery, 1960s
      1 film reel: col.; 3 inch, in 7 inch can.; Note on reel: Shots of Artifacts recovered from Monitor site by US Navy LCU. (Film made in port.) Film is edited. Note on can: Color Original. See file cards for detailed contents of each reel. Each reel is labeled in abbreviated fashion.; Numbered: C-164-A, Reel 2 of 3; Duplication Master: Beta SP. UA88-57-4
      - Original 16mm motion picture film (Box 15, Film-reel UA27020001-F16-0058)
    - U.S.S. Monitor Discovery, 1960s
      1 film reel: col.; 3 inch, in 5 inch can.; Note on reel: Film made from U.S. Navy videotape of Monitor on ocean floor. Poor quality. Edited. Note on can: Color Original. See file cards for detailed contents of this reel. The reel itself is labeled in abbreviated fashion.; Numbered: C-164-B, Reel 3 of 3; Duplication Master: Beta SP. UA88-57-4
      - Original 16mm motion picture film (Box 15, Film-reel UA27020001-F16-0059)
    - Monitor: Ship returns to port, 1960s
      1 film reel: 3 inch.
      - Original 16mm motion picture film (Box 16, Film-reel UA27020001-F16-0071)
    - This is Duke Univ.: Color, Orig. (Silent), 1960s
      1 film reel: 7 inch in 10 inch can.
      - Original 16mm motion picture film (Box 37, Film-reel UA27020001-F16-0074)
    - Campus Scenes: Homecoming, "Old Homecoming", 1960s
      7" reel; Numbered: C-145
      - Original 16mm motion picture film (Box 14, Film-reel UA27020001-F16-0118)
    - Gown Fitting, 1961; 16mm, color, silent; 0:02:51
      - Original 16mm motion picture film (Oversize-film-can 5, Film-reel UA27020001-F16-0196)
      - Digital video preservation file (Digital-materials UA27020001-SET-0111, Video-file UA27020001-F16-0196.mkv)
      - Digital video access file (Digital-materials UA27020001-SET-0111, Video-file UA27020001-F16-0196.mp4)
    - Unknown, 1961-01
      - Original 16mm motion picture film (Box 20, Film-reel UA27020001-F16-0197)
    - Unknown, 1961-02
      - Original 16mm motion picture film (Box 20, Film-reel UA27020001-F16-0198)
    - Practice - Rochester & T. Mooyman, 1961-07
      - Original 16mm motion picture film (Box 20, Film-reel UA27020001-F16-0204)
    - Symphony, circa 1961; 16mm, color, silent; 0:02:26
      - Original 16mm motion picture film (Oversize-film-can 5, Film-reel UA27020001-F16-0201)
      - Digital video preservation file (Digital-materials UA27020001-SET-0114, Video-file UA27020001-F16-0201.mkv)
      - Digital video access file (Digital-materials UA27020001-SET-0114, Video-file UA27020001-F16-0201.mp4)
    - Chapel inside, Choir, East Dorm, circa 1961; 16mm, color, silent; 0:01:35
      - Original 16mm motion picture film (Oversize-film-can 5, Film-reel UA27020001-F16-0203)
      - Digital video preservation file (Digital-materials UA27020001-SET-0116, Video-file UA27020001-F16-0203.mkv)
      - Digital video access file (Digital-materials UA27020001-SET-0116, Video-file UA27020001-F16-0203.mp4)
    - Univ. Outtakes, circa 1962; 16mm, color, silent; 0:01:43
      - Original 16mm motion picture film (Oversize-film-can 5, Film-reel UA27020001-F16-0205)
      - Digital video preservation file (Digital-materials UA27020001-SET-0117, Video-file UA27020001-F16-0205.mkv)
      - Digital video access file (Digital-materials UA27020001-SET-0117, Video-file UA27020001-F16-0205.mp4)
    - Marine Lab Aerials, 1963; 16mm, black-and-white, silent; 0:02:52
      1 film reel: 3 inch, in 7 inch can.; Numbered: C-11
      - Original 16mm motion picture film (Box 13, Film-reel UA27020001-F16-0018)
      - Digital video preservation file (Digital-materials UA27020001-SET-0023, Video-file UA27020001-F16-0018.mkv)
      - Digital video access file (Digital-materials UA27020001-SET-0023, Video-file UA27020001-F16-0018.mp4)
    - Dedication Dates are set for Duke's new Law School Bldg., 1963-04-26
      1 film reel: 3 inch, in 7 inch can.; Numbered: C-1
      - Original 16mm motion picture film (Box 13, Film-reel UA27020001-F16-0014)
    - Dedication Dates are set for Duke's new Law School Bldg., 1963-04-26
      - Original 16mm motion picture film (Box 13, Film-reel UA27020001-F16-0015)
    - Aerial Shots of Football Stadium, 1963-09-24; 16mm, black-and-white, silent; 0:01:50
      1 film reel: 3 inch, in 7 inch can.; Numbered: C-2
      - Original 16mm motion picture film (Box 13, Film-reel UA27020001-F16-0016)
      - Digital video preservation file (Digital-materials UA27020001-SET-0022, Video-file UA27020001-F16-0016.mkv)
      - Digital video access file (Digital-materials UA27020001-SET-0022, Video-file UA27020001-F16-0016.mp4)
    - Campus Scenes, circa 1963; 16mm, color, silent; 0:05:37
      1 film on core, no reel, in 7-inch can.; Numbered: C-29
      - Original 16mm motion picture film (Box 13, Film-reel UA27020001-F16-0026)
      - Digital video preservation file (Digital-materials UA27020001-SET-0028, Video-file UA27020001-F16-0026.mkv)
      - Digital video access file (Digital-materials UA27020001-SET-0028, Video-file UA27020001-F16-0026.mp4)
    - Law School Left Overs, circa 1963; 16mm, black-and-white, silent; 0:03:51
      - Original 16mm motion picture film (Oversize-film-can 5, Film-reel UA27020001-F16-0206)
      - Digital video preservation file (Digital-materials UA27020001-SET-0118, Video-file UA27020001-F16-0206.mkv)
      - Digital video access file (Digital-materials UA27020001-SET-0118, Video-file UA27020001-F16-0206.mp4)
    - Eastward Launching: Original Color & Outtakes, 1964; 16mm, color, silent; 0:02:36
      1 film on core, no reel, in 7-inch can.; Numbered: C-22
      - Original 16mm motion picture film (Box 13, Film-reel UA27020001-F16-0019)
      - Digital video preservation file (Digital-materials UA27020001-SET-0024, Video-file UA27020001-F16-0019.mkv)
      - Digital video access file (Digital-materials UA27020001-SET-0024, Video-file UA27020001-F16-0019.mp4)
    - Convocation, 1964
      1 film on core, no reel, in 7-inch can.; Numbered: C-28
      - Original 16mm motion picture film (Box 13, Film-reel UA27020001-F16-0025)
    - Eastward Launching, A Roll, 1964-09
      1 film on core, no reel, in 7-inch can.; Numbered: C-100
      - Original 16mm motion picture film (Box 13, Film-reel UA27020001-F16-0032)
    - Eastward Launching, B Roll, 1964-09
      - Original 16mm motion picture film (Box 13, Film-reel UA27020001-F16-0033)
    - Aerial Survey, 1964-10; 16mm, black-and-white, silent; 0:01:51
      1 film reel: 3 inch, in 7 inch can.; Labeled: Campus Scenes. Aerial view of Duke Forest and West Campus, B&W-Orig. PxR.; Numbered: C-23
      - Original 16mm motion picture film (Box 13, Film-reel UA27020001-F16-0020)
      - Digital video preservation file (Digital-materials UA27020001-SET-0025, Video-file UA27020001-F16-0020.mkv)
      - Digital video access file (Digital-materials UA27020001-SET-0025, Video-file UA27020001-F16-0020.mp4)
    - Aerial Survey, 1964-10; 16mm, black-and-white, silent; 0:02:53
      1 film reel: 3 inch, in 7 inch can.; Labeled: Campus Scenes. Aerial view of Duke Forest. Also shots of plane, Orig. Rev. B Numbered: C-23
      - Original 16mm motion picture film (Box 13, Film-reel UA27020001-F16-0021)
      - Digital video preservation file (Digital-materials UA27020001-SET-0026, Video-file UA27020001-F16-0021.mkv)
      - Digital video access file (Digital-materials UA27020001-SET-0026, Video-file UA27020001-F16-0021.mp4)
    - Aerial Survey II, 1964-10; 16mm, color, silent; 0:02:50
      1 film reel: 3 inch, in 7 inch can.; Reel is labeled: Campus Scenes. Aerial view of W Campus (shaky), Flying at chapel, Color workprint-Ink edge nos.; Numbered: C-26
      - Original 16mm motion picture film (Box 13, Film-reel UA27020001-F16-0024)
      - Digital video preservation file (Digital-materials UA27020001-SET-0027, Video-file UA27020001-F16-0024.mkv)
      - Digital video access file (Digital-materials UA27020001-SET-0027, Video-file UA27020001-F16-0024.mp4)
    - Eastward's First Cruise: TV release, 1 min., Ship leaving port, Dr. Menzies, Dr. Bonhout, 1964-11
      1 film reel (1 min.): 3 inch, in 7-inch can.; Numbered: C-25
      - Original 16mm motion picture film (Box 13, Film-reel UA27020001-F16-0022)
    - Eastward: B&W Prints, 1964-11
      1 film on core, no reel, in 7-inch can.; Numbered: C-25
      - Original 16mm motion picture film (Box 13, Film-reel UA27020001-F16-0023)
    - Response to Our Challenge, 1965; 16mm, color, sound; 0:21:27
      - Original 16mm motion picture film (Box 19, Film-reel UA27020001-F16-0127)
      - Digital video preservation file (Digital-materials UA27020001-SET-0064, Video-file UA27020001-F16-0127.mkv)
      - Digital video access file (Digital-materials UA27020001-SET-0064, Video-file UA27020001-F16-0127.mp4)
    - Glee Club, 1965 circa; 16mm, black-and-white, silent; 0:01:54
      - Original 16mm motion picture film (Oversize-film-can 6, Film-reel UA27020001-F16-0229)
      - Digital video preservation file (Digital-materials UA27020001-SET-0134, Video-file UA27020001-F16-0229.mkv)
      - Digital video access file (Digital-materials UA27020001-SET-0134, Video-file UA27020001-F16-0229.mp4)
    - Oceanography, A Roll, 1965-01-27
      1 film on core, no reel, in 7-inch can.; Numbered: C-101
      - Original 16mm motion picture film (Box 14, Film-reel UA27020001-F16-0034)
    - Oceanography, B Roll, 1965-01-27
      - Original 16mm motion picture film (Box 14, Film-reel UA27020001-F16-0035)
    - Regional Center for the Study of Aging (Used by Peggy Mann Show): Dr. Eisdorfer, 1965-03-26
      1 film on core, no reel, in 7-inch can.; Numbered: C-51
      - Original 16mm motion picture film (Box 13, Film-reel UA27020001-F16-0028)
    - Eastward 800 ft. Rev. Orig. Rev. w/print with ink edge nos. Also, Kenneth Galbraith, 1965-04
      1 film on core, no reel, in 10-inch can.; Numbered: C-46
      - Original 16mm motion picture film (Box 37, Film-reel UA27020001-F16-0027)
    - Fund Raising, Fifth Decade Campaign Announcement: Dr. Knight, Wright Tisdale, George Allen, 1965-06-09; 16mm, black-and-white, sound; 0:03:36
      1 film reel: 7 inch.; Numbered: C-53
      - Original 16mm motion picture film (Box 13, Film-reel UA27020001-F16-0029)
      - Digital video preservation file (Digital-materials UA27020001-SET-0029, Video-file UA27020001-F16-0029.mkv)
      - Digital video access file (Digital-materials UA27020001-SET-0029, Video-file UA27020001-F16-0029.mp4)
    - Art Museum, circa 1965; 16mm, black-and-white, silent; 0:00:51
      1 film reel: 3 inch, in 7-inch can.; Numbered: C-158
      - Original 16mm motion picture film (Box 14, Film-reel UA27020001-F16-0051)
      - Digital video preservation file (Digital-materials UA27020001-SET-0035, Video-file UA27020001-F16-0051.mkv)
      - Digital video access file (Digital-materials UA27020001-SET-0035, Video-file UA27020001-F16-0051.mp4)
    - Art Museum, circa 1965; 16mm, black-and-white, silent; 0:00:34
      - Original 16mm motion picture film (Box 14, Film-reel UA27020001-F16-0052)
      - Digital video preservation file (Digital-materials UA27020001-SET-0036, Video-file UA27020001-F16-0052.mkv)
      - Digital video access file (Digital-materials UA27020001-SET-0036, Video-file UA27020001-F16-0052.mp4)
    - Campus Scenes, circa 1965; 16mm, color, silent; 0:01:13
      - Original 16mm motion picture film (Oversize-film-can 6, Film-reel UA27020001-F16-0223)
      - Digital video preservation file (Digital-materials UA27020001-SET-0128, Video-file UA27020001-F16-0223.mkv)
      - Digital video access file (Digital-materials UA27020001-SET-0128, Video-file UA27020001-F16-0223.mp4)
    - TV Feature: Deep Sea Mineral Deposits, Dr. Orin Pilkey, 1966-05
      1 film reel: 7 inch.; Numbered: C-95
      - Original 16mm motion picture film (Box 13, Film-reel UA27020001-F16-0031)
    - Response to Our Challenge, 1966-05-23; 16mm, color, silent; 0:08:25
      1 film on core, no reel, in 7-inch can.; Numbered: C-89
      - Original 16mm motion picture film (Box 13, Film-reel UA27020001-F16-0030)
      - Digital video preservation file (Digital-materials UA27020001-SET-0030, Video-file UA27020001-F16-0030.mkv)
      - Digital video access file (Digital-materials UA27020001-SET-0030, Video-file UA27020001-F16-0030.mp4)
    - Campaign Announcement: Original, Outtakes, 1966-06; 16mm, black-and-white, silent; 0:05:38
      1 film on core, no reel, in 7-inch can.; Numbered: C-124
      - Original 16mm motion picture film (Box 14, Film-reel UA27020001-F16-0036)
      - Digital video preservation file (Digital-materials UA27020001-SET-0031, Video-file UA27020001-F16-0036.mkv)
      - Digital video access file (Digital-materials UA27020001-SET-0031, Video-file UA27020001-F16-0036.mp4)
    - Eastward Cruise: Dr. Orin Pilkey, 1966-06
      1 film reel: 3 inch. in 7-inch can.; Note on reel: Orig. Rev. Mag. stripe/silent.; Numbered: C-129
      - Original 16mm motion picture film (Box 14, Film-reel UA27020001-F16-0037)
    - Original color Eastward outtakes, 1967
      1 film reel: 3 inch, in 7-inch can.; Numbered: C-142
      - Original 16mm motion picture film (Box 14, Film-reel UA27020001-F16-0040)
    - Duke Marine Lab, Beaufort: Research, Limnoria, Dr. R. Menzies, 1967
      1 film reel: 3 inch, in 7-inch can.; Numbered: C-144
      - Original 16mm motion picture film (Box 14, Film-reel UA27020001-F16-0043)
    - Dr. Menzies of Duke on a section of Dead Sea off N. C. Coast, 1967-01-23
      1 film, no reel, no core, in 7 inch can.; Numbered: C-142
      - Original 16mm motion picture film (Box 14, Film-reel UA27020001-F16-0041)
    - Dr. Menzies of Duke on new Panama Canal Problems, 1967-01-24
      1 film reel: 3 inch, in 7-inch can.; Numbered: C-143
      - Original 16mm motion picture film (Box 14, Film-reel UA27020001-F16-0042)
    - Campus Scenes, circa 1967; 16mm, color, silent; 0:02:22
      - Original 16mm motion picture film (Oversize-film-can 6, Film-reel UA27020001-F16-0224)
      - Digital video preservation file (Digital-materials UA27020001-SET-0129, Video-file UA27020001-F16-0224.mkv)
      - Digital video access file (Digital-materials UA27020001-SET-0129, Video-file UA27020001-F16-0224.mp4)
    - Nuclear Structure Lab: Moving Accelerator from RR Building, 1968-02-05
      1 film reel: 3 inch, in 7-inch can.; Numbered: C-157
      - Original 16mm motion picture film (Box 14, Film-reel UA27020001-F16-0050)
    - Nuclear Structure Lab: Moving Accelerator from RR Building, 1968-02-05
      1 film reel: 3 inch, in 7-inch can.; Numbered: C-151
      - Original 16mm motion picture film (Box 14, Film-reel UA27020001-F16-0055)
    - Duke Homestead Dedication, 1968-04-28; 16mm, black-and-white, silent; 0:02:54
      1 film reel: si., b&w; 3 inch, in 7-inch can.; Label on can: List of order of shots is enclosed. See Audio Tape #B-650 for sound of this event. [This list is in Box 14, Folder 12.]; Numbered: C-160
      - Original 16mm motion picture film (Box 14, Film-reel UA27020001-F16-0054)
      - Digital video preservation file (Digital-materials UA27020001-SET-0038, Video-file UA27020001-F16-0054.mkv)
      - Digital video access file (Digital-materials UA27020001-SET-0038, Video-file UA27020001-F16-0054.mp4)
    - Study-In in Allen Building, 1969
      1 film reel: b&w; 7 inch.; Numbered: C-150
      - Original 16mm motion picture film (Box 14, Film-reel UA27020001-F16-0049)
    - Doing Good: A Roll Original, 1969; 16mm, color, silent; 0:09:40
      - Original 16mm motion picture film (Box 15, Film-reel UA27020001-F16-0065)
      - Digital video preservation file (Digital-materials UA27020001-SET-0043, Video-file UA27020001-F16-0065.mkv)
      - Digital video access file (Digital-materials UA27020001-SET-0043, Video-file UA27020001-F16-0065.mp4)
    - Doing Good: B Roll Original, 1969; 16mm, color, silent; 0:09:54
      - Original 16mm motion picture film (Box 15, Film-reel UA27020001-F16-0066)
      - Digital video preservation file (Digital-materials UA27020001-SET-0044, Video-file UA27020001-F16-0066.mkv)
      - Digital video access file (Digital-materials UA27020001-SET-0044, Video-file UA27020001-F16-0066.mp4)
    - Blacks Seize Allen Building, 1969-02-13
      1 film reel: si., b&w; 3 inch, in 7-inch can.; Note on can: Pictures began approx 4:30 p.m. -Police and Tear Gas- B&W Original; Numbered: C-136; Reference Copy: VHS. UA88-57-13; Reference Copy: DVD. UA88-57-13
      - Original 16mm motion picture film (Box 14, Film-reel UA27020001-F16-0039)
    - Terry Sanford's first news conference after being named President of Duke University, 1969-12-14; 16mm, color, sound; 0:03:34
      1 film reel: 5 inch, in 7 inch can.; Numbered: D-4; Duplication Master: Beta SP. UA88-57-5; Highlights of Terry Sanford's first news conference appear on Duplication Master: Beta SP. UA88-57-12; Highlights of Terry Sanford's first news conference appear on Reference Copy: VHS. UA88-57-12
      - Original 16mm motion picture film (Box 15, Film-reel UA27020001-F16-0062)
      - Digital video preservation file (Digital-materials UA27020001-SET-0041, Video-file UA27020001-F16-0062.mkv)
      - Digital video access file (Digital-materials UA27020001-SET-0041, Video-file UA27020001-F16-0062.mp4)
    - Duke Film, 1969 circa; 16mm, color, silent; 0:01:43
      - Original 16mm motion picture film (Oversize-film-can 6, Film-reel UA27020001-F16-0226)
      - Digital video preservation file (Digital-materials UA27020001-SET-0131, Video-file UA27020001-F16-0226.mkv)
      - Digital video access file (Digital-materials UA27020001-SET-0131, Video-file UA27020001-F16-0226.mp4)
    - Terry Sanford Inauguration, 1970; 16mm, color, sound; 0:07:58
      1 film reel: 7 inch.; Note on can: Descriptions of shots are enclosed. [Typed and hand-written shot list removed from can and placed in Folder 4, Box 15.]; Numbered: D-2, Reel 1 of 2; Duplication Master: Beta SP. UA88-57-6; Highlights of Terry Sanford's inauguration appear on Duplication Master: Beta SP. UA88-57-12; Highlights of Terry Sanford's inauguration appear on Reference Copy: VHS. UA88-57-12
      - Original 16mm motion picture film (Box 15, Film-reel UA27020001-F16-0060)
      - Digital video preservation file (Digital-materials UA27020001-SET-0039, Video-file UA27020001-F16-0060.mkv)
      - Digital video access file (Digital-materials UA27020001-SET-0039, Video-file UA27020001-F16-0060.mp4)
    - Terry Sanford Inauguration, 1970; 16mm, color, sound; 0:10:04
      1 film reel: 7 inch.; Note enclosed in can: Entire reel is portions of Sanford's speech (see Reel 2 designation on handwritten list of shots in can with #D-2, Reel 1, for more detailed list of quotes which are on the film. [Typed and hand-written shot list removed from can and placed in Folder 4, Box 15.]; Numbered: D-2, Reel 2 of 2; Duplication Master: Beta SP. UA88-57-7; Highlights of Terry Sanford's inauguration appear on Duplication Master: Beta SP. UA88-57-12; Highlights of Terry Sanford's inauguration appear on Reference Copy: VHS. UA88-57-12
      - Original 16mm motion picture film (Box 15, Film-reel UA27020001-F16-0061)
      - Digital video preservation file (Digital-materials UA27020001-SET-0040, Video-file UA27020001-F16-0061.mkv)
      - Digital video access file (Digital-materials UA27020001-SET-0040, Video-file UA27020001-F16-0061.mp4)
    - Duke Gardens, 1970-04-22; 16mm, color, silent; 0:02:49
      1 film reel: si., col.; 3 inch, in 7-inch can.; Numbered: C-159
      - Original 16mm motion picture film (Box 14, Film-reel UA27020001-F16-0053)
      - Digital video preservation file (Digital-materials UA27020001-SET-0037, Video-file UA27020001-F16-0053.mkv)
      - Digital video access file (Digital-materials UA27020001-SET-0037, Video-file UA27020001-F16-0053.mp4)
    - Football: Florida vs. Duke, 1970-09-12
      - Original 16mm motion picture film (Box 20, Film-reel UA27020001-F16-0207)
    - Football: Duke - Virginia, 1970-09-26
      - Original 16mm motion picture film (Box 20, Film-reel UA27020001-F16-0208)
    - Football: Duke - West Virginia, 1970-10-10
      - Original 16mm motion picture film (Box 20, Film-reel UA27020001-F16-0209)
    - Football: Duke - N. C. State, 1970-10-17
      A mimeograph listing scenes from this film is in Folder 9, Box 20. Players mentioned are Leo Hart, Dan Phelan, Billy Thompson, Steve Jones, Dave Wright, Rich Searl, Dick Biddle, Ernie Jackson, and Tom Ussery.
      - Original 16mm motion picture film (Box 20, Film-reel UA27020001-F16-0210)
    - Football: Duke - South Carolina, 1970-11-14
      A mimeograph listing scenes from this film is included in Folder 9, Box 20. Players mentioned are Art Bosetti, Leo Hart, Wes Chesson, Bob Parrish, Brad Evans, Bill Baker, and Dick Biddle.
      - Original 16mm motion picture film (Box 20, Film-reel UA27020001-F16-0211)
    - Football: Duke - North Carolina, 1970-11-21
      - Original 16mm motion picture film (Box 20, Film-reel UA27020001-F16-0212)
    - Campus Scenes, 1970s; 16mm, color, silent; 0:01:30
      - Original 16mm motion picture film (Oversize-film-can 5, Film-reel UA27020001-F16-0213)
      - Digital video preservation file (Digital-materials UA27020001-SET-0119, Video-file UA27020001-F16-0213.mkv)
      - Digital video access file (Digital-materials UA27020001-SET-0119, Video-file UA27020001-F16-0213.mp4)
    - China reel 1, 1970s
      note with films apparently reads "Friendship through sports opens door to China"; "Summers and Davies there in China for friendship"; "Dick Williams interpreter"; "Sponsored by State Dept. Kissinger and [China ??]"; "'68, '72 summer [could be swimmer] medalists"
      - Original 16mm motion picture film (Box 39, Film-reel UA27020001-F16-0244)
    - China reel 2, 1970s